<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on AlosarBlog</title>
    <link>https://alosarjos.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on AlosarBlog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://alosarjos.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bad times</title>
      <link>https://alosarjos.github.io/posts/bad-times/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alosarjos.github.io/posts/bad-times/</guid>
      <description>Things have gone bad, and somehow I think this should be also reflected here. Things have gotten worse personally and I couldn&amp;rsquo;t find the will to keep working and reading about Rust. Thankfully because of the time I spend moving to work and going back I&amp;rsquo;ve been reading a book about what means to focus and to work deeply. Hopefully tyhis will help somehow&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Almost rusted</title>
      <link>https://alosarjos.github.io/posts/almost-rusted/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alosarjos.github.io/posts/almost-rusted/</guid>
      <description>Last chatpers of the book remain&amp;hellip; The final multithread server project looks really fun to make, can&amp;rsquo;t wait for it. I still need to complete the advanced features chapter (If Smart pointers and concurrency weren&amp;rsquo;t advance enough&amp;hellip;).
Once this is finished I still don&amp;rsquo;t know if going for my own personal project, or if going to Rust by example. Will check later the contents of this book.
Anyways, while not being even close to know Rust, one can see so easily why people like it&amp;hellip; Hoping I can get a job where I can use it!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting rusty</title>
      <link>https://alosarjos.github.io/posts/getting-rusty/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alosarjos.github.io/posts/getting-rusty/</guid>
      <description>This first week has been pretty productive, but still I need to get better on reducing the time I take for a break. I don&amp;rsquo;t know if people do actually spend more than 2 hours just reading in front of their screens whitout their eyes itching.
I got up to chapter 11 on the Rust book and I either it&amp;rsquo;s contents have been updated since the last time I read it or I&amp;rsquo;m kinda getting details I didn&amp;rsquo;t on previous attemps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello world</title>
      <link>https://alosarjos.github.io/posts/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alosarjos.github.io/posts/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>This is the first step into learning the technologies I want to learn. The first step into a better self organization and discipline. If this blog lives, then my journey is going through the right way, if this is dead, then that means I failed.
I&amp;rsquo;ve worked for quite some time on an Android app called BackLogger, sadly it never got out from beta, and befcause of the deprecation of it&amp;rsquo;s external APIs and the change in the authentication for the data retrieval I&amp;rsquo;m forced to redo quite some work on it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
